AUSTIN KEVIN SULLYMAN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER/GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Contact

- Kaduna
- **** 0909 766 3506
- 0708 392 5957
- austinsullyman@gmail.com
- f /Austin SK

Profile

A versatile and hardworking and analytical IT personnel with a "get the job done fast and efficiently" mentality who always preservers to achieve the best results. Passionate about how IT processes are carried out. I also have 3 years of work experience both as a freelancer and working in an organization.

Experience

IT ASSISTANT

Garkuwa Specialist Hospital, Kaduna | 2018

Worked as an assistant to the head of the IT department. Was giving the duty of inputting and updating data into the hospitals database and also troubleshoot certain problems that occurred on the hospitals systems.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER/GRAPHIC DESIGNER

EasyAce Synergy, Abuja | 2021 - Present

Working as a front-end developer and graphic designer. My duties here involve working on the frontend of websites (UI & Ux) and making banners, social media posters, logos, and animations for different brands and companies

PRODUCT DESIGN

Easyace Synergy, Abuja | 2022 - Present

Working as the head of the product designs team. In charge of overseeing the process of creating products to meet clients' expectations.

Personal information

Name

Austin Sullyman

Gender

Male

Residence

Lagos

Nationality

Nigerian

Marital Status

Single

State of Origin

Kogi, Lokoja L.G.A

Additional activities

- Playing Sports.
- Exploring the internet and carrying out research.
- UI/UX designing.
- **Gaming.**
- Listening to music.

Achievements

Achievement

Graduated with a 2:2 degree in Information Technology.

Skills

Professional Skills

Java PHP

React

Node.is

HTML

UI/UX

Web Designing

Photoshop

Graphic Designing

Personal Skills

Problem Solving
Time Management
Communication
Leadership
Interpersonal
Teamwork
Critical Thinking



Education

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Accra Institute of Technology, Accra | 2015 - 2020

Studied information technology as my first degree, majoring in Multimedia/Graphic designing and Networking Systems.

SECONDARY SCHOOL EDUCATION

Second Ecwa, Kaduna | 2015

Completed my secondary school education.

SECONDAY SCHHOL EDUCATION

Adeyemo College of Arts and Sciences, Kaduna | 2013 - 2015 Attended classes SS1 - SS2.

SECONDARY SCHOOL EDUCATION

Zamani College, Kaduna | 2010 - 2013

Attend Junior Secondary School here.

Resposiblities

BAND LEADER

Adeyemo College of Arts and Sciences, Kaduna | 2014

ASSISTANT SOCIAL PREFECT

Adeyemo College of Arts and Sciences, Kaduna | 2015

HEAD OF PRODUCT DESIGNS

Easyace Syneegies, Abuja | 2022 - Present

Interests



I enjoy watching and participating in sports.

Researching

Researching and exploring on the Internet, continue to pursue this interest by reading a diverse range of texts. Keeping up to date with new technologies in respect to web development and graphic designs.